Wrege, Charles D. Collection of International Management Institute Correspondence 6271
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Charles D. Wrege Collection of International Management Institute Correspondence
1925- 1986
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Wrege, Charles D.
International Management Institute (IMI)
6271
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Correspondence.
6343673
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 07, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Biographical / Historical
Charles "Chuck" Wrege finished his undergraduate degree in Upsala College, obtained his Masters degree at the New School fo Social Research and another Masters of Business Administration and his Ph.D. at NYU. He taught industrial management at Rutgers University for 30 years. He became a renowned historian, researcher and writer. He is regarded as a "National Treasure" by many in his field because of his expertise and the seminal research he has done in the area of management history.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Deviant, Paul; Filene, Edward; Gerduk, Nettie; Wrege, Charles D.; International Management Institute; League of Nations; Twentieth Century Fund
6343673
- Paper on IMI for 1986 Academy of Management Centennial. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Not Used.
- Gerduk, Nettie. Twentieth Century Fund., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Deviant, Paul to Edward Filene. IMI., 1925-1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Correspondence.
- Deviant, Paul to Edward Filene. IMI., 1926 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- IMI Letters., 1926 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- IMI Letters., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Report. IMI., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- IMI Letters., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- IMI Letters., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- IMI Letters., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- IMI Letters., 1932 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- IMI Letters., 1933 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- IMI Letters., 1934 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- IMI. Work Done for the League of Nations., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 14)